What's up, guys? So, today we're going
to be trying out a tool called Nano
Banana Pro [music] and how it can turn a
snapshot into a studio-like photography
with almost no setup. Now, we still have
a long way to go before Nano Banana Pro
can replace real photographers, but for
social media content and experimenting
with ideas, it is really [music] useful
and really easy to do. So, I actually
went to the grocery store and grabbed a
few random products straight off the
shelf, just everyday items, and I took
photos of them with no lighting and no
professional camera, just with my phone
alone. And today, we're going to see if
we can turn those into eye-catching
product shots [music] using Nano Banana
Pro. First up is the Tira Mr. Chocolate.
The picture I took is pretty basic,
[music] uh, overhead lights, no styling
and such. If you want to use Nano Banana
Pro, head over to Google Gemini [music]
and at the bottom you can see a tiny
banana icon [music] and it says create
image. If we click on it, now we're
using Nano Banana Pro. So what I'm going
to do now is that I want to take those
[music] reference photos that I took
over here. So when we are working with
Nano Banana Pro, it's really important
to [music] always snap different angles
so that Nano Banana Pro knows how your
product looks like for the best product
consistency.
I want to select all four product photos
over here and drag and drop into Nano
Banana Pro. So I want to select create
image. And now we [music] are using Nano
Banana Pro in Google Gemini. So let's
type in a prompt to prompt our [music]
image. Let's start with the background.
Golden luxury gradient background.
Professional
product
photography.
Luxury premium vibe.
Tira misu
powder exploding
behind
some hazelnuts [music]
surrounding
the product.
Uh studio photography,
professional lighting
and professional
product commercial photography.
4K.
So once we are done with our prompt,
[music] we're just going to hit enter
and then we wait.
Now this is the results. I would say
it's pretty good. So if we look at the
original photo, the details is really
well preserved. The logo [music] remains
the same. Tiramisu almond dark chocolate
that remains the same as well. the logo,
[music] the packaging itself, even the
crease on the box
is still intact. And at the bottom left
corner, [music] we have an icon that
says cheese that is preserved as well.
So, I'm very surprised that it got the
reflection down as well. Overall, I
would say this looks pretty solid for
social [music] media use. So, now that
we have downloaded our photo, let's take
a closer look of the image itself. If we
zoom in, the resolution is not [music]
actually like really high res. Uh, we
have a lot of noise going on. It's
[music] kind of blurry.
It's good for social media, but it's not
really good [music] enough if you would
like to print it out. If you want to
print it out on a brochure, if you want
to print it out on maybe as a menu, a
physical menu, it's probably not enough.
[music] It's not high- res enough to do
it. But for social media viewing, it's
probably fine. So let's say if you don't
like this [music] image itself, uh you
can always type in give me another
variation and hit enter and you can get
another variation of the same product.
Look at that.
It has [music] some cream over here
which I'm I did not request this. But
overall the product itself is [music]
still pretty solid. The product is very
consistent. the packaging, the design
itself really good. What is good about
Nano Banana Pro is that you can actually
talk with it, have a conversation
[music] with it like a designer would.
So I can just type in remove the
white [music] cream
and enter. So it can maintain the
original photo while removing the cream.
So you get something that is very
similar [music]
with an updated prompt. All right, look
at that. That is [music] great.
So, the next thing we want to try out
is, can we turn it into a [music]
lifestyle photography? Something usable
for Instagram or maybe post it on your
IG stories to promote your product. So,
let's type in a prompt. Put the product
uh beside the window.
some
sunlight shining through. We get some
window shadows
design uh Muji vibes
and
uh iPhone look. Enter.
All right, look at that. That looks
really good.
So, can we change the aspect ratio?
change the [music] aspect ratio to 45.
All right. And [music] we can change the
aspect ratio really, really easily. It
has some terramisu on the box. I think I
want to clean it up. Uh remove the terra
[music] misu
uh stain
on top [music] of the box. It's okay to
have it on the table, but not on the
box. All right,
that looks really good. Yeah, that's
pretty solid. It looks really good. So,
now we're going to try our second
product, which is a [music] Thai ketchup
from our grocery store. So, same thing.
We're going to start with the
background. Uh, generate a professional
product photography.
The background is spicy [music] red. And
we have some chili [music] and garlic
flying surrounding the product.
Professional
product photography
uh studio lighting.
The product is floating in the middle of
the frame.
Enter.
Look at that.
This is really, really solid. This is
really good. The reflection is good. The
overall lighting, the composition,
everything is pretty good. [music] Can
we change the resolution to maybe like
one by one? uh change the aspect ratio
to one by one. We want to do a square
photo. So, let's try it out.
And look at that. We have a square
version that we can use on social media.
If you know a little bit of Photoshop,
if you know a little bit of Canva, this
is really useful for you to use. Saves a
lot of time. Now, let's bring it to the
kitchen.
Put the product at the kitchen. The
kitchen is mostly
white. Maybe give it like a 16 by9.
Enter.
All right, this is good. But somehow the
product is still floating. So, put the
product down on the table. Look at that.
This looks really, really good. So,
let's level this up a bit.
Have some
light rays shining through
the window.
Look at that. That is straight up
looking really good. [music]
But I also noticed that the more uh you
generate, the more you continue the
conversation, the resolution, the
details of the product itself, it gets
blurriier and blurriier. So it might
work [music] if you turn on the new chat
and get very specific on what you want
to prompt on the first try. [music] So
let's head over to our final product,
which is a great tea. This is also a
random tea, Armat T London, that I got
from the shelf itself. [music] And for
this one, it even has the price tag
still intact on the packaging. So, can
we remove it with Nano Banana [music]
Pro? Let's try it out. So, we're going
to do something that is similar. a
wooden table setting with some ear gray
tea leaves
surrounding the product.
Uh aesthetic vibes, a cup of o gray tea
and a [music]
classic teacup.
Uh aspect ratio 4x5.
Let's try it out. All right, now you got
it right. This looks really decent.
So, you have the right photo. It removed
the price tag. [music] The packaging is
correct. It also has a free spoon icon
over here, which [music] is also in the
original product packaging itself. So,
after running a few random grocery store
items, [music] here's my takeaway. Nano
Banana Pro is really good at turning
simple rough photos into something that
is visually polished, but it is not
production [music] ready yet. It is not
perfect and definitely not a replacement
for real photographers. [music]
Not now. But that's not a point here.
So, what is so exciting about Nano
Banana Pro is [music] how it evolves the
creative process. If you're a small
brand, a small business, just starting
[music] out, if you want to turn uh
basic snapshots photo on [music] your
phone and turn it into something that is
visually appealing, this is really good.
There's still a long way to go if you
want to use all these photos for fine
prints [music] or if you need higher
resolution, better textures, it's just
not there yet. But for everyday posting,
it's [music] good enough. So it also
makes you wonder where could all these
technology [music] be going to in the
next one or two year. It's crazy. So
yeah, Nano Banana Pro, it's not perfect.
It's not magic, but it really [music]
opens the door to a lot of possibilities
in the future. If you want to see me
push it further, try out more AI
technologies, or even compare it with a
real actual photo shoot, feel free to
subscribe, like, [music] and comment on
this video. Tell me what you think.
Thanks for watching. My name is Ryan Wei
and I'll see you in the next video.